What is your Orthodoxy?  I don’t
В чём твоё православие? Нека
believe in God.  Just what kind?
верую в Бога. Только какого?
Jesus Christ.  Understood.  When was he born?
Иисус Христу. Понял. Когда он родился?
January 6th.  And did he die?  The sixth.  And he died,
6 января. А умер? Шестого. А умер,
but I don’t know that.
но я этого не знаю.
Hello, Abuba.
Здравствуйте, Абуба.
Let's have a normal conversation.
Давай нормально пообщаемся.
And I communicate normally.  What is that
А я нормально общаюсь. А что это у тебя
thing you have in your nose?
за приспособотка в нос?
What?
Что?
And this, well, look, I’m not saying this right away, these are
А это, ну, смотри, это не сразу говорю,
new ones, in short.  This is to pierce the nose,
это новые короче. Это нос пробивать,
in short, some kind of cartridge.
короче, картридж какой-то.
Why do you get your nose pierced?   To
А для чего пробиваешь нос?
have, so that there
Чтобы меть, чтобы
would be a joke for me.  How old are you?  Don't get
ме шутка была. Сколько тебе лет? Не
sick.  I have a lot.  How many?
болеть. Мне много. Сколько?
Why do you need this information?  Well, if
А зачем вам эта информация? Ну, если
you're 18, let's chat.
есть 18, пообщаемся.
Well, I'm 18. I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky.   Are
Ну, я мне 18. Я из города Хмельницкий.
you from Russia?  Where?
Ты из России? Откуда?
From Russia I am in Saratov.  How do you communicate
Из России я в Саратове. А чем общаешься
here?
тут?
Well, it's just interesting.  And who are you teaching?  Well, this is a
Ну, интересно просто. А на кого учи? Ну
big one.  And I am a riverman, a
тут это большой. А я речник,
riverman, a
ручник,
riverman.  You know, you talk like that, like.   Yes,
речник. Знаешь такие речи ведёшь, типа.
yes.  Yes.  That is, you are giving a kind of
Дадада. Да. То есть типа провозглашаешь
festive speech there.
речь там праздничную такую.
Well, yes.  Can you give some kind of speech?
Ну да. А можешь какую-то речь сказать?
Well, I mean, I just have a route.  This is a
Ну в смысле, я только маршрут. Это
private.
рядовой.
Well, like you make up all sorts of speeches,
Ну, типа ты всякие речи составляешь,
performances, yes,
выступления, да,
which you watch, now I’ll explain it to you like this
которую вот смотрите, сейчас я вам так
.  Marines, you know, that's what it's like.
объясню. Морпехи вот, знаете, вот такое.
But I don’t travel by sea, but by river.
Только не я не по морю ездю, а по речке.
Oh, you're like a sailor.  Sailor?  Yes, yes.  Yeah,
А, типа ты матрос. Матрос? Дадада. Да,
well, like a sailor.  River sailor.  Understood.
ну, типа матрос. Речной матрос. Понял.
Cool.  Good job, huh?  I
Прикольно. Хорошая работа, да? Мне тоже
like it too.  Understood.  How much do they pay?
нравится. Понял. Сколько платят?
Well, as a student, I get paid 40.
Ну я как студент мне 40 платит.
Where do you go and swim?  Fine.
А ходишь куда плаваешь? Нормально.
And we are a ferry, in short, we sail from one
А мы переправа, короче, плаваем с одного
end of the city to the other.  So you're
конца города до другого. А то есть ты
like a minibus driver, like a conductor in a
как водитель маршрутки, как кондуктор в
minibus, that is, well, in a minibus
маршрутке, то есть, ну, в маршрутке
boat,
корабликом,
right?  Yes, yes.  Yes.  All.  That is, you
да? Дадада. Да. Всё. То есть выпра
transfer passengers from one bank to the
пассажиров переводите с одного берега на
other.  Understood.  All.  Yes, yes.  Yes.  Then just
другое. Понял. Всё. Дадада. Да. То так и
say so.  I work on a water minibus,
скажи. Работаю типа в маршрутке водной,
or rather a riverboat operator.  Well, yes.
а то речник. Ну да.
Tourist
Туристическая
work on these Americans was recently
работу на вот недавно этих американцев
taken for a ride.  Well, I get it.
катали. Ну понял.
Listen, why do you think Russia is fighting
Слушай, как считаешь, зачем Россия воюет
with Ukraine?
с Украиной?
Well, that's funny.
Ну прикол.
Emly Russians take away.  Well, like
Эмли русские забрать. Ну как типа
ancient Rus' or something like that.  What
древняя Русь там что-то такое. А что там
's there?  Well, I don't
такое? Ну я не
know.  I mean, where?  What is
знаю. В смысле, что где? А что такое
Ancient Rus'?  Can you tell me?
Древняя Русь? Можешь сказать мне?
Well, Orthodox people are the same.  Well,
Ну это православные люди такие же. Ну
just curious, right?  It's called Little Russia
просто интересно, да? Малоруссия
.  Yes.  Well, like, I’m
называется. Угу. Ну типа я я
Orthodox, and are you Orthodox too
православный, а ты тоже православный,
?  Well yeah, that's cool.  Do you know the 10
что ли? Ну да, прикольно. А знаешь 10
commandments?
заповедей?
No.  And what is your Orthodoxy?
Нет. А в чём твоё православие?
[music]
[музыка]
I believe in God.  But in which one?
Верую в Бога. Только в какого?
Jesus Christ.  Understood.  When was he born?
Иисус Христу. Понял. Когда он родился?
January 6th.  And did he die?  The sixth.  And he died.
6 января. А умер? Шестого. А умер.
Well, I don't know that.  Well, like, there is
Ну я этого не знаю. Ну типа ж есть ээ
Christ's birthday and his death day.  Well,
день рождения Христа и день смерти. Ну
yes.
да.
Well, what kind of Orthodox are you that you don’t
Ну то что ты за православный, что не
know the day of
знаешь день смерти
Christ’s death?  I understand, I understood from reading.
Христа? Понял, понял начитанно.
He died on June 22.  Understood.  And how did he die?
умер. Понял. А как он умер?
Crucify.  And he was crucified.  So, why was
Распяти. А его распятили. Так, а за что
he crucified?
его распяли?
for the fact that he is his he is from how to
за то, что он его он из как
explain sins.  Well, because of sin, because of
объяснить грехов. Ну, из-за грехо из-за
all the sins of humanity.  Well, he
всех грехов человечества. Ну вот он же
took it.  Well, why did they crucify him?
взял. Ну его распяли за что?
Why did they crucify him?  For human sins.
А за что распяли? За грехи человечески.
Right.  Right.  Yes.  But look,
Правильно. Правильно. Да. А вот смотри,
here was ancient Rus', where in ancient
вот была древняя Русь, где в древней
Rus' they crucified Jesus.
Руси распяли Иисуса.
Jerusalem.  No, well, a suburb of Jerusalem.
Иерусалим. Нет, ну пригород Иерусалима.
This was ancient Rus'.  Thus, Jerusalem
Это древняя Русь была. Так, Иерусалим
was part of ancient Rus'.  What was the name of the suburb of
входил в древнюю Русь. А пригород
Jerusalem where Christ was crucified
Иерусалима, где распяли Христа, как
?  Palestine.  No,
назывался? Палестина. Нет,
Constantinople.  But Constantinople didn’t
Константинополь. А это А Константинополь
understand this.  And how much?  For example, you and I are
понял. А сколько? Вот ты, например, я
simply Orthodox, right?  I even
просто православный, да? Я ещё даже в
worked a little in the church.  Hey, do you
церкви немножко работал. Э, может, ты
know how many years ago Jesus was born?
знаешь, сколько лет назад родился Иисус?
Well, that's how it was born 25 years ago.  2025
Ну вот как зародился 25 лет назад. 2025
years ago.  Well, it's called the era of humanity
лет назад. Ну, эра человечество
, yes.  Eh, the era of humanity.
называется, да. Э, эра человечества.
Yes.  Understood.
Угу. Понял.
And how many years
А умер сколько лет
ago did he die?  At what age did you know how?
назад? В каком возрасте умел? Умер
Jesus died.
Иисус.
At a young age.  How old was he?  16
В молодом возрасте. Сколько ему было? 16
or 17?
или 17?
No, more.  23, right?
Не, побольше. 23, правильно?
years old.  Okay, okay.  What was the name of
года. Так, хорошо. А как звали жену
Jesus
Иисуса
Christ's wife?  He didn't have it.  Was.
Христа? У него у него не было. Было.
Mary Magdalene.  Look.
Мария Магдалина. Посмотри.
Marina Magdalena.  Mary Magdalene was,
Марина Магдалина. Мария Магдалина была,
yes, the wife of Jesus Christ.  They had no children
да, женой Иисуса Христа. Детей у них не
, but they had a wife.
было, жена была.
Well, look, what commandments did
А что, смотри, какие заповеди принёс
Jesus Christ bring to you, which you are
Иисус Христос тебе, которые ты
studying?  Commandments.
исследуешь? Заповеди.
Well, there are seven commandments.  Please, please
Ну, есть семь заповедей. Угоди
, yes,
там, да,
[music]
[музыка]
some kind of pleasure.  No, I'm just
угодия какие-то. Не, мне просто
curious, look, it's not very good
интересно, смотри, я же не очень хорошо,
that I met you, an Orthodox, too, you
что я встретил тоже тебя православного,
understand?  We all, these
понимаешь? Мы все нас вот эти
Americans, the Anglo-Saxons want to set our
американцы, англосаксы хотят наши
Orthodox peoples at odds and make us
православные народы рассорить и чтобы мы
renounce Orthodoxy.  They want to
изреклись православие. Они же хотят нас
convert us, in short, to some of their faiths, you
обратить, короче, в какие-то свои веры,
understand?
понимаешь?
And it’s good for us that there are people like
А а мы хорошо, что вот есть такие, как
you, who seek Orthodoxy, like, and
ты, которые ищучат православие, типа, и
carry it in their souls
в своей душе несут
.  This is very You have a
его. Это очень У вас сейчас мусульман
lot of Muslims now, they are supposedly against Orthodoxy.
много, они типа против православия.
Well yes, there are those who are against it.  Yes.
Ну да, есть такие, которые против. Да. А
Which Orthodox saints do you
каких ты каких ты православных святых
know?
знаешь?
Things Oleg.  That's right, things Oleg.  So,
Вещи Олег. Правильно, вещи Олег. Так,
who else?
кто ещё?
Rurik.
Рюрик.
Rurik.  So, who else are the Orthodox
Рюрик. Так, кто ещё из православных
saints?
святых?
which
который
Russian
русский
Kiev Kyiv
кие киевский
now Vladimir some kind of it seems.  Yes,
сейчас Владимир какой-то вроде бы. Да,
something is holy, my sun.
что-то свято солнышко.
Holy sun.  No, wait, now I’ll
Свято солнышко. Не, подожди, сейчас я
remember
вспомню
Rurikovich.  He just named Rurik.
Рюрикович. Рюрика он сейчас назвал.
Wait.  Yes, Vileg Rurik.  Who else
Подожди. Да, Вилег Рюрик. Да кто ещё
was there?   Do
был?
you know for sure?  Exactly.  Yes.  Here I am now.
Ты точно знаешь? Точно. Да. Вот я сейчас
Exactly, exactly, you can.  He's
Точно, точно, можно. Он ещё такой
something else.  Batu.
что-то. Батый.
Who is Batu?  Saint Batu.
Кто Батый? Святой Батый.
I remember something like that, right?  There was Batu.
А что-то я так помню, да? Был Батый.
Who else?  What other saints do you know?
Кто ещё? Каких ещё знаешь святых?
Nicholas
Николай
Archangel Michael.  Archangel Michael the
Архангел Михаил. Архангел Михаил
Miracle Worker Archangel Michael.
Чудотворец Архангел Михаил.
No, Archangel Michael is not a saint,
Нет, так архангел Михаил это не святой,
he is an archangel.  He's in heaven, like, with the
это архангел. Он на небе типа с
angels.
ангелами.
Yes, I also tell us that Brawl Stars is
Да я тоже нам скажите Brawl Stars
playing.  Look, how do you, as an
играет. А смотри, ты как ты как
Orthodox Christian, know the Bible, well, at least
православный Библию, ну, знаешь хоть
a little bit?  No, I haven't read it.  And why?
немножко? Нет, не читал. А из-за чего?
Why did God banish Adam and Eve and Eve
Из-за чего Бог изгнал Адама и Ева и Еву
to the earth to make
на землю,
snakes?  Okay, no, wait,
чтобы змейкутель. Так, не, подожди,
guys, don't give me hints.  Tell the boys,
пацаны, не подсказывай. Скажи пацанам,
don't give hints.  Yes, we are talking to you
не подсказывают. Да, мы с тобой же
.  I
говорим. Мне
wonder if anyone here has
интересно, если кто-то Я тут великий шар
gone crazy.  Well, he really wanted to know the Bible well
пошёл. Ну он прямо хорошо хотел Библию
.  Just ask him.  No, no,
знать. Вот спросите у него. Не, не, вот
look, what do you think, are you Orthodox?  Come on,
удя, как ты считаешь, ты православ? А ну
give me this Orthodox one.  I
давай сюда мне этого православный. Я
dream, well, to send this.  Well, love,
сни, ну, чтобы послать это. Ну, любовь,
I guess, somehow.  Right.
наверное, както. Правильно.
Help me, help me.
Помогите мне, помоги мне.
Got it, got it.  What did Eve pick from the
Понял, понял. А что сорвала Ева с
tree?   The
дерева?
apple was poisoned.  No, I took a bite out of the
Яблоко отравила. Нет, отку откусила
apple.  Right.  I took a bite of the apple.   It is
яблоко. Правильно. Откусила яблоко.
impossible and she died.  She wasn't allowed.  Yes,
Нельзя и умерла. Ей нельзя было. Да её
they gave her paradise.  So good.  She died.
рай выдарили. Так хорошо. Она умерла. А
What did Adam do next?   The
что дальше делал Адам?
snake ate him and bit him.  Don't know.
Его змея съела, укусила. Не знаю.
So how, how did they resurrect the dead Eve
А так А как э как мёртвую Еву
?
воскресили?
Marinated and cooked.  Well, it
Замариновали, приготовили. Ну там же
was there, well, it was like a coffin.  And Adam
было, ну это же было, что гроб. И Адам
had to kiss her three times on the
должен был поцеловать её три раза в
lips.  And then she will wake up from the spell, from
губы. И она тогда проснётся от чар, от
this apple.   I do
этого яблока.
n’t know, I don’t know anything about this. Well, it’s
Не знаю, что-то я такое не Ну это же ещё
been like that since childhood.  Eva bit the apple, didn't she?
с детства было. Ева укусила яблоко, да?
Fell into a coma, huh?  She died, yes.  O. And in order for
Упала в кому, да? Умерла, да. О. И для
him to say to her, God: "You must
того, чтобы он её Бог сказал: "Ты должен
kiss her three times,
поцеловать её трижды
Eve."  Adam was like, "Oh, [ __ ], she's
Еву". Адам такой типа: "Блин, так она же
dead."  It's like he's saying, "Trust me
мертва". Типа он говорит: "Доверься мне
and kiss me three times."  He kissed her twice
и поцелуй трижды." Он её два раза
, hesitated the third time, but
поцеловал, третий засомневался, но
kissed her anyway.  And she
всё-таки поцеловал. И она
lived.
жила. А
Hush, don't say that.  Hey,
да тише, не говори так. Эй,
what did you want to say?
что хотел сказать?
Yes.  And
Угу. А на
what about, for example, where is Koschei the
что, например, ээ вот в Библии Кощей
Deathless mentioned in the Bible?
Бессмертный где вспоминается?
And babaga.  Baba Iga.  No, Baba Iga is a
А бабага. Баба Ига. Не, Баба Ига - это
tale from fairy tales.  And Koschei is
сказ из сказок пришло. А Коще
immortal from the Bible.
бессмертный из Библии.
What verse?  Which page?  This same
Какой стих? Какая страница? Это ж этот
King David fought with Goliath and with the
царь Давид ещё с Галиафом бился и с
immortal Koschei.
Кощеем бессмертных.
Well, it was written in the Bible, which
Ну это в Библии было написано, какой
verse, which page.  Gospel of
стих, какая страница. Евангелие от
Andronius 148.
Андрония 148.
148.
148.
Why do I honestly not care about anything?
Что я честно не шаюсь чму?
Maybe you have some kind of Old Believers?  Well,
Может, у вас староверие какое-то? Ну,
which one is this, by the way?  This is the Old Testament, the
это какое, кстати? Это ветхий завет,
New Testament.  Old.  Old.
Новый Завет. Ветхий. Ветхий.
Ah, well, I have some old ones, in principle.  I
А, ну у меня ветхи есть, в принципе. Я
don't know, I can.  There are different editions.
не знаю, могу. Там есть разные редакции.
There is one translated from Aramaic into
Есть с арамейского переведённый на
Greek, and one in Aramaic.   It
греческий, есть на арамейском.
was different.  Well, here's another
По-разному был. А вот хорошо такой ещё
interesting question, guys.  Uh, how do
интересный вопрос, ребята. Ээ, как вот
you know from the Bible why, let's say
вы по Библии знаете, из-за чего скажем,
, Eve, yes, cheated on Adam?
ээ, Ева, да, изменила Адаму?
She didn't cheat on him, well, it's like the
Она ему не изменяла, ну, типа ей
tempter, the snake biter, sort of tempted
искуситель, змейкуситель типа подстрёг
her to bite the apple.  Because of this, she is
её откусить яблоко. Из-за этого её
Israeli.  No, no, that's Yes.  They were thrown to the ground
израит. Не, не, это Да. Их на землю
, and on the ground she had already betrayed
скинули, а на земле она уже изменила
Adam.
Адаму.
Why?
Почему?
Really long.
Реально долго.
Well, I don't have any others.  Well, after that,
Ну у меня нет других. Ну и после этого
Cain killed Abel.
Каин убил Авеля.
So, I mean, who would he
Так, в смысле, как с кем бы ему
cheat on with if there were two of them, like Adam and Eve,
изменило, если их двое, типа Адам и Ева,
two people with whom?  With hand.  Okay,
два человека с кем? С рукой. Так,
wait, listen.  Well, okay, but how did
подожди, слушай. Ну, а хорошо, а как у
their children have children?
ихних детей дети появлялись?
Chinkeen was quiet.
Чинькинь было тихо.
Well, you can't do it any other way.  Well, like,
Ну, по-другому ты никак. Ну, типа прямо
who exactly did Eve cheat on Adam with?
вот с кем изменила Ева Адаму?
Me what?
Я что?
Well, Adam had, Adam had a son Ham,
Ну, у Адама был, у Адама был сын Хам,
right?  Because of this there is also the name
да? Из-за этого ещё вот есть название
Hamkha.  Yes.  So Eve cheated on
Хамха. Да. Вот Ева изменила с хамом
Adam with a boor.
Адаму.
Hamom.
Хамом.
Yes, I heard.   This is the
Да, слышал.
first time in my life I've heard it
Я ещё я первый раз в жизни слышал
at all.
вообще.
Why did God destroy Sodom and Gomorrah?
А за что Бог уничтожил Содом и Гомору?
Who is this
Это кто
anyway?  I know that Judas sold Jesus
вообще? Я знаю, что Иисуса Иуда продал
for 30 silver coins.
за 30 серебряных монет.
Yes.  Well, look how Yes, when Jesus
Да. Ну смотри, как Да, когда Иисус
entered Sodom and Gomorrah, yes, he was
входил в Содом и Гомору, да, ему там
refused admission there, yes.  From And why
отказали в приёме, да. Из А почему
exactly did God destroy this city then?
именно Бог уничтожил тогда этот город?
Well, he would be like, hello, like, Jesus is for peace
Ну он бы так алё, типа, Иисус же за мир
throughout the world, kindness for evil.  So, what
во всём мире, доброта на зло. Так, а
were Sodom and Gomorrah for?   I
Содом и Гомора были за что?
honestly don't know.  Understood.  They just
Честно не знаю. Понял. Они как раз
wanted to build an empire and conquer the whole
хотели империю построить, завоевать весь
world.  Ah, that's funny.
мир. А, прикол.
Understood.
Понял.
Why were they called Sodom and Gomorrah?
А почему они назывались Содом и Гомора?
Why was Jesus named Jesus?  Well,
А почему Иисуса назвали Иисусом? Ну
exactly the same question.  I don’t mean
точно такой же вопрос. Я не потому что
because the state of Sodom and Gomorrah,
потому что государство Содом и Гомора,
yes, by the names of the rulers.  There was
да, по названиям правителей. Там был
this ruler of Sodom, and in this one was the
этот правитель Содом, а в этом была
ruler of
правительница
Gomorrah.  Okay, okay, I get it.  You know.
Гомора. Так, так, понял. Знатьте.
Okay, that's it.
Так, всё.
What was the name of the child of Sodom and Gomorrah?
А как звали ребёнка Содома и Гоморы?
I don't know who Sodom and Gomorrah is.  You
Я не знаю, кто такой Содома и Гомора. Ты
are asking me about their children.  Well, well,
меня спрашиваешь за их детей. Ну что, ну
this is a famous famous character.
это известный известный персонаж.
Tell this Hercules, probably.  Yes, I'm
Скажи этот Геракл, наверное. Да, я тебя
giving you a ride.  This is generally one of the virgins of these
катаю. Это вообще это из девст вот этих
examples.  Ah, well, I don't know.  Either Ida or
приклади. А, ну хз. Либо Ида, либо у
I have no other options.  No.  Uh,
меня других нет вариантов. Нет. Ээ,
Sacher Masoch.
Захер Мазох.
I don't even know about that.  This is the first
А я такого даже не знаю. Я вообще первый
time I've heard of such a set-book.  Well, that
раз такой наборбук слышал. Ну то, что
it's Sacher Masoch, right?  He was the son of Sodom
это Захер Мазох, да? Он был сыном Содома
and
и
Gomorrah.  Yes.  Danik water.  Well, that's cool,
Гоморы. Да. Даник воды. Ну прикольно,
that's cool.  I didn't know.
прикольно. Не знала.
Well, you're bad.  Come on, give me this one, I'll
Ну ты плохо. А ну дай дай мне с этим, я
talk to the biblical one.  Who knows their
с библейским поговорю. Кто шарит в
Bible?  Let him sit down and I'll talk to him
Библии? Дай пусть он сядет, я с ним
.  I'm
поговорю. Мне
interested.  Yes.  Well, yeah, go ahead.
интересно. Да. Ну да, давай.
No, no, no need in front of him.  Now
Нене не перед ним не надо. Сейчас
for Are you also Orthodox?  Yes.  Yeah, that's
за Ты тоже православный? Да. Да,
cool.  Well, the cross, in short, turned black along
прикольно. Ну крестик, короче, почернел
with the chain.  In short, I took it off.  Well, I'll put it on
с цепочкой. Я её снял, короче. Ну я
later, when I've taken off the
одену потом, когда Ну в смысле снял
new one.
новую.
Well, I'll say it again, my cross and the
Ну у меня, говорю ещё раз, крестик с
target turned black from the water.  I
целячкой почернели от воды. Я их
cleaned them.  It's not the water that makes it black, it's the
почистил. Это не от воды чернеет, это от
heart that's callous.
сердца чёрство.
What is your nationality?
А ты по национальности кто?
Well, probably Russian.  I don't know,
Ну, наверное, русский. Я не знаю, честно
honestly.  What do you mean, probably?  Well, you
на самом деле. В смысле, наверно? Ну, ты
speak so uncertainly.  Now, now.
так неуверенно говоришь. Сейчас, сейчас.
Yes, I know who my ancestors are asking for
Да я знаю, с кем у меня предки прошу
forgiveness from.  Well, mom and dad, what were your
прощения. Ну, мама и папа, кто были по
nationalities?
национальности?
What are you doing here?  I'm talking.  Get out
Что ты тут делаешь? Разговариваю. Выходи
of here.  Get out of here.  Get out of here.
отсюда. Пошла отсюда. Пошла отсюда.
Really nice
Право славненько
[laughter]
[смех]
finished.  That's how they all are.  Because
закончили. Вот так они все. Потому что
Orthodoxy is Orthodoxy of things.  Oleg
православие православие вещи. Олег
Rurik like, subscribe
Рюрик лайк, подписка
comment.  Subscribe to my Telegram right
комент. Підпишись на мій Telegram прям
away.  Here it is.  And
зараз. Ось він. А
the priest is even more and more important.  YouTube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо. YouTube
is throwing us into a dark ban.
заганяе нас через карки в тіньовий бан.
And even though the video is not shown to people,
И дуже багато відео не показуется людям
information about the stream is often not shown
вчасно не показуеться інформація про
.  So, in order to get a
стрими. Тому для того, щоб ми мали
quick connection, sign up right
оперативный зв'язок, підпишиться прямо
away.  And the message there in the telegram is
зараз. А попик там в телеграмі окмде ще
still useful and valuable information, and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація и мы
obliged to provide you with a permanent
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational connection regardless of what
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того,
YouTube shows you about it.  Glory to
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube. Слава
Ukraine!  Subscribe.
Україні! Підпишись.